<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Homepage on The FCI Company</title><link>https://thefci.company/</link><description>Recent content in Homepage on The FCI Company</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-uk</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 20 Dec 2018 13:44:55 +1000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://thefci.company/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Accuracy</title><link>https://thefci.company/services/accuracy/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://thefci.company/services/accuracy/</guid><description>We strive for the highest standards of accuracy for both our product and our process.
Delivering full configuration interaction levels of theory offers insight into the fundamental interactions within your system of interest; and we will compose wonderfully with QC/MM toolkits to offer accuracy on demand.
Further, we follow the highest development standards to deliver reliable results. From formal model checking in Alloy, property testing with Hypothesis and the use of the correct-by-construction languages Bluespec and Rust, we aim to deliver highly performing tools on time.</description></item><item><title>Speed</title><link>https://thefci.company/services/speed/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://thefci.company/services/speed/</guid><description>A bosonic ground state of a system of electrons is trivial to find; they would attach to the most electropositive atom centre in the system, and become a condensate. Unfortunately for us, electrons are fermions and cannot occupy the same state - they experience fermi pressure to spread out, occupying higher energy states and generating chemical structures we can use.
The central difficulty of full configuration interaction calculations is solving the sign problem.</description></item><item><title>Coral Westoby</title><link>https://thefci.company/team/coral-westoby/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Dec 2018 13:44:55 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://thefci.company/team/coral-westoby/</guid><description>Coral has degrees in Computer Science and Theoretical Physics. She realised the need for truly accurate chemical simulations as a early employee at Riverlane, and found the ideal platform in reconfigurable logic shortly thereafter.</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>https://thefci.company/about/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2018 17:01:34 +0700</pubDate><guid>https://thefci.company/about/</guid><description>THe FCI company believes automated drug discovery relies on fast and accurate tools for learning chemical behaviour.
In-sillico screening is used to find &amp;ldquo;hits&amp;rdquo;, possible drug candidates. Current automated drug discovery tools can produce vast numbers of leads, but the majority of spend in drug development is on failures during live trials, with only 1 out of 8 drugs that start live trials resulting in a licence application[1].
Existing computational chemistry tools can provide excellent agreement with experiment when interpreted by experts, but have narrow domains of applicability[2][3].</description></item><item><title>Contact</title><link>https://thefci.company/contact/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2018 17:01:34 +0700</pubDate><guid>https://thefci.company/contact/</guid><description/></item></channel></rss>