<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Services on The FCI Company</title><link>https://thefci.company/services/</link><description>Recent content in Services on The FCI Company</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-uk</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://thefci.company/services/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Accuracy</title><link>https://thefci.company/services/accuracy/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://thefci.company/services/accuracy/</guid><description>We strive for the highest standards of accuracy for both our product and our process.
Delivering full configuration interaction levels of theory offers insight into the fundamental interactions within your system of interest; and we will compose wonderfully with QC/MM toolkits to offer accuracy on demand.
Further, we follow the highest development standards to deliver reliable results. From formal model checking in Alloy, property testing with Hypothesis and the use of the correct-by-construction languages Bluespec and Rust, we aim to deliver highly performing tools on time.</description></item><item><title>Speed</title><link>https://thefci.company/services/speed/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://thefci.company/services/speed/</guid><description>A bosonic ground state of a system of electrons is trivial to find; they would attach to the most electropositive atom centre in the system, and become a condensate. Unfortunately for us, electrons are fermions and cannot occupy the same state - they experience fermi pressure to spread out, occupying higher energy states and generating chemical structures we can use.
The central difficulty of full configuration interaction calculations is solving the sign problem.</description></item></channel></rss>